carnegolflinks.com 2018-08-21

# PRIVACY POLICY

PRIVACY POLICY
Carne Golf Links have created this privacy statement to demonstrate our absolute
commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and
dissemination practices of Carne Golf Links.
A user can access our web site and utilise a number of our services without
providing any information at all. However, all users who avail of Carne Golf Links
online services and opt in services provide basic contact and demographic
information. We do not provide this information to any third party.
If users wish to contact Carne Golf Links regarding our reservations and services,
they must enter personal information. Services that currently require some form
of sign up include:
   * Reservations
   * Contact Us email enquiries
   * Subscription to Carne Golf Links newsletter
The information collected when a user contacts Carne Golf Links regarding a
service can include an e-mail address and name. When contacting us regarding a
service, a user may also "opt out" of various e-mail notifications or offers (see
Opt- Out Procedures below).
Certain online purchase options require users to give us financial information
(such as their credit card numbers), and demographic information (such as their
address etc.). Financial information that is collected is used solely to bill the user
for products and services.
Information Automatically Logged:
We use your IP address, log user agents and referring address to help diagnose
problems with our server, to administer our Web site and to identify unique
users. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information. We
do not provide our log file data to any third party.
Irish Data Protection Commissioner:
Further information on your data privacy rights are available on the website of
the Irish Data Protection Commissioner.
E Mail :
Using the e-mail addresses provided on forms and online purchases – Carne Golf
Links periodically sends promotional e-mail to its subscribers about specials

offered by Carne Golf Links. You can indicate on all forms that you wish not to
receive further e-mail information from Carne Golf Links.
External Links:
This site contains links to other sites. Carne Golf Links is not responsible for the
privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Security:
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration
of the information under our control. Unfortunately, no data transmission over
the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to
protect your personal information, carnegolflinks.com cannot ensure or warrant
the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or
services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we
make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.
Opt-Out:
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/
marketing information from Carne Golf Links. To unsubscribe please go to the
unsubscribe page and enter your e-mail address.
Contacting the Web Site:
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, or the security practices
of this site, you can contact: info@carnegolflinks.com
